LEMON GAUTAM

Front End Developer

**** +977-9861-000-213 **♀** Chandragiri-13, KTM @ azulgautam79@gmail.com

Ø github.com/lemongautam79

SUMMARY

Senior front-end developer with 7+ years of experience designing and building responsive web design and mobile apps in the financial industry. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved code and design.

EXPERIENCE

2014 - 2018

Front End Developer

Scottsdale, AZ

Bouchard

Bouchard is a residential real estate technology company launching their first app this summer. The app will allow consumers to see homes on demand via UBER-like technology. #SEEHOMESFAST

- · Implemented performance tuning techniques on stored procedures and back-end queries which resulted in 46% improvement in application performance
- · I had the responsibility to train 4 people the front-end basics and helped them develop further
- · Worked with an agile team of 12 members and provided end-to-end solutions for clients

2012 - 2014

Scottsdale, AZ

Junior Front End Developer

DocHub

- · Created 4 application to solve problems among the society
- · Ensured end to end process of data extraction until reporting and noted efficiency of close to 25%
- · Developed my team-work skills by working in close collaboration with 6 other students

EDUCATION

2010 - 2014

Master of Science in Management **Arizona State University**

TECH STACK

C# Unity IS React React Toolkit/RTK Query Git